

Applicant for:

# [Remote] Senior Software Developer (.NET, ReactJS)

Futurify 27 March 2024

# Thành Công

☑ leduythanhcong@gmail.com

Main interests: .NET, C#

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

- Good English communication
- Experience on: Asp.net, .net core, MVC, MS SQL, Entity framework, Reactjs, microservices, git,...

<sup>&</sup>quot;Hiring the wrong person is the most costly mistake you can make." - Brian Tracy







### **CONTACT ME AT**

leduythanhcong@gmail.com

https://www.facebook.com/cong.ldt

0394322259

**\(\text{\dec}\)** 03/05/1999

Cau Giay, Ha Noi, Viet Nam

#### PASTIMES AND ACTIVITIES

- Reading technical in Medium, Stackoverflow and other IT blogs.
- Studying programming in Pluralsight.
- Playing games and guitar.
- Watching movies.

# LE DUY THANH CONG

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER APPLY POSITION: FULLSTACK

### CAREER PROFILE

I'm a software engineer with 5 years of C#.Net technologies expertise. In spite of having a bachelor's degree in computer science, my first job required me to utilize C# which I fell in love. As a result, I was motivated to learn C#.

I'm always up for a challenge and studying new languages and technologies. This position is an excellent match with my skills and experience. I am confident that I can make a significant contribution to your organization.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

# Programming languages

• C# .Net, C++, Javascript

# Frameworks/ Platforms

- ASP.NET MVC, Web API
- ReactJs, Angular, Typescript/Javascript
- Entity Framework
- MicroService Architecture
- Azure Cloud: Service bus, Azure function, Storage
- DocuSign, Blob trigger, Event Trigger, Queue

# **Database Management Systems**

- MS SQL Server, SSMS
- MongoDB Compass
- MS Azure Storage Explorer

#### Version Control

• Git

# Soft skills

- Teamwork
- Good English communication

# EDUCATION

University of Information Technology, Vietnam National University Ho Chi Minh City

# Sep 2017 - June 2021

- Departure: Computer Science
- Major: Computer Vision
- Bachelor of Computer Science

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Technical Architect

FPT Software | May 2023 - Present

# Product: PenproPlus, Nicho

<u>Feature 1:</u> Contribute to the development of the system architecture, enhance performance optimization, and establish a flexible backend structure.

- Spearheaded the development and maintenance of the back-end infrastructure utilizing ASP.NET Web API, ensuring optimal performance and a flexible architecture.
- Played a key role in crafting dynamic data structures to enhance system efficiency and adaptability.
- Implemented performance optimization strategies, including caching mechanisms and the creation of shared functions, contributing to a streamlined and high-performing back-end system.
- Assessed and critiqued the coding standards of team members to uphold a high level of code quality and consistency.
- Collaborated with the project team to gather comprehensive user requirements and translated them into technical designs for seamless implementation.
- Applied Agile/Scrum development methodologies to foster an iterative and collaborative work environment, ensuring efficient project delivery.

<u>Technology:</u> .NET Core, .NET, Angular, DocuSign, Azure Function, Blob, Queue, Background Job.

Team size: > 130 members

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Fullstack Developer

NASHTECH | July 2022 - May 2023

#### **Product: Insurance**

<u>Feature 1:</u> Take on the backend of the CRM web application:

- Developed and maintained multiple web-based applications using ASP.NET MVC and .NET CORE.
- Worked with the project team to gather user requirements and create technical designs.
- Developed and implemented algorithms to improve the performance of the applications.
- Designed and implemented SQL Server database schemas, including stored procedures.
- Familiarity with Agile/Scrum development methodologies.

<u>Technology:</u> .NET Core, .NET MVC, Angular, Typescript/Javascript, MicroService Architecture, React, Dapper, SQL Server, XML generated, MS Unit Testing, CI/CD.

# Feature 2: Document management

• When a customer purchases a product on the CRM or public website, the document system sends them the documents. It is my responsibility to manage this system, which includes investigating issues, fixing them, and providing support to other products.

Technology: .NET 5, AWS EventProcessor, Queue, MS Unit Testing, CI/CD

Team size: 30 members

# Feature 3: Public site management

• The end user has the ability to purchase policies through the public site. My responsibility involves managing this page, which includes tasks such as creating policy holders and policies. Additionally, I am responsible for developing the front-end of the policy holder management page using Angular.

<u>Technology:</u> ASP.NET MVC, Angular, Typescript/Javascript, SQL Server.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer

Novaon | Nov 2021 - July 2022

# **Product: CRM - Customer Relationship Management**

Feature 1: Take on the backend of the Project module:

- Database design
- Implement CRUD, get Users of Project, add Deal to Project
- Authorization this module
- Handle the influence of this module on anothers module
- Fix bugs

Technology: ABP Framework, DDD design pattern, Code first, EntityFramework, Automapper.

Feature 2: Write report and export data to excel file.

• There are 2 main reports that I am responsible for, which are employee reports and revenue reports

Technology: Dapper, EntityFramework.

Feature 3: Create data from server to server.

<u>Technology:</u> HttpFactory.

Feature 4: Fix bug and add feature in Frontend.

<u>Technology</u>: ReactJs.

Team size: 10 members

# WORK EXPERIENCE

**Backend Developer** 

Gannha.com | April 2019 - Oct 2021

#### **Product: E-Commerce**

<u>Responsibility:</u> Participant in Product teams to implementing APIs and fixing bugs. Some outstanding features such as:

- Discount management (CRUD)
- Product management (CRUD, Duplicate SKU checking)
- Manufacturer management (CRUD)
- Product attribute management (CRUD)
- Payment online

Technology: CQRS pattern, MongoDB, .NET 3.1

# **Product: Organization, User Management.**

<u>Responsibility:</u> Implementing service layer, writing and testing APIs, and then writing documents for these APIs in **Postman/Insomnia**. Some outstanding features such as:

• User, organization management (CRUD, Duplicate Checking Email/Phone, Active/Deactive,..)

<u>Technology:</u> SQL, EntityFramework, Microsoft.AspNetCore.Identity, .NET 5.

Team size: 10 members